bluelinkmarketing.com 2016-06-23

# Bluelink Marketing - Welcome

### Privacy Policy

Your privacy is important to us and we have prepared this Privacy Policy to explain how we collect, use and protect Personal Information (defined below) and Non-Personal Information (defined below) when you use the Bluelink Marekting Website and your choices for managing your information preferences. This Privacy Policy covers online privacy and data protection practices of the Bluelink Marekting Website. By using the Bluelink Marekting Website, you signify your consent to this Privacy Policy and the Terms and Conditions of Use posted on the Bluelink Marekting Website. This Privacy Policy applies to all users of the Bluelink Marekting Website. 

#### 1\. Managing Your Information Preferences.

You may review, correct, update, or change your Personal Information, or remove your Personal Information from our direct marketing efforts, at any time by changing the relevant setting in your Bluelink Marekting profile or by contacting us by emailing us info@BluelinkMarekting.com. If you have questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy, please contact us the same way.

#### 2\. Information We Collect

(a) Personal Information. We collect information that personally identifies you, such as your name, username, email address, credit card details, and such other information as we may from time to time request ("Personal Information") only if you choose to share such information with us. For example, you may be asked to provide us with certain Personal Information when you register with the Bluelink Marekting Website, when you download and register Bluelink Marekting Software and at other times. The decision to provide this information is optional; however, if you elect not to register or provide such information, you may not be able to access certain content, features, or services available on or through the Bluelink Marekting Website.

(b) Non-Personal Information. We automatically collect anonymous usage information that does not identify an individual user ("Non-Personal Information") to help us understand how users use the Bluelink Marekting Website. For example, each time you use the Bluelink Marekting Website we automatically collect the type of Web browser you use, your operating system, your Internet Service Provider, your IP address, the pages you view, and the time and duration of your visits to the Bluelink Marekting Website.

(c) Cookies and Web Beacons. We use cookies (a small file containing a string of characters that uniquely identifies your Web browser) and Web beacons (an electronic file placed within a Web site that monitors usage). We use cookies and Web beacons to improve the quality of the Bluelink Marekting Website. Most Web browsers are initially set up to accept cookies, but you can reset your Web browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, certain features of the Bluelink Marekting Website may not work if you delete or disable cookies. Some of our Service Providers (described below) may use cookies and Web beacons in connection with the services they perform on our behalf. 

#### 3\. How We Use Personal And Non-Personal Information We Collect.

(a) General. We use Non-Personal Information and Personal Information for internal purposes only, such as to notify you of new products or services, to send service notifications, to customize the advertising and content you see, to fulfill your requests for products and services, to improve the Bluelink Marekting Website, to conduct research, to solicit your feedback and input about the Bluelink Marekting Website, and to provide more relevant products, services, and advertisements on or through the Bluelink Marekting Website. Non-Personal Information and Personal Information may be combined with data collected from other sources so that we may further improve the relevance of products, services, and advertisements offered on or through the Bluelink Marekting Website. We will not sell, share or rent Personal Information to third parties, and we will not otherwise disclose Personal Information to third parties, without your express permission or as expressly disclosed in this Privacy Policy.

(b) Service Providers. From time to time, we might establish a business relationship with other persons or entities whom we believe trustworthy and whom we have asked to confirm that their privacy practices are consistent with ours ("Service Providers"). For example, we may contract with Service Providers to provide certain services, such as credit card processing, advertising, analytics tools, widget providers, DNS providers, data management services, Web hosting, and Web development. We provide our Service Providers with only the information necessary for them to perform these services. Each Service Provider must agree to implement and maintain reasonable security procedures and practices appropriate to the nature of the information involved in order to protect your information from unauthorized access, destruction, use, modification or disclosure. Service Providers are prohibited from using Personal Information for purposes other than as specified by Bluelink Marekting.

(c) Standard Analytics Information. We may use, and disclose to third parties, certain Non-Personal Information regarding the Bluelink Marekting Website (e.g., number of visits, page views, number of registered members who reside in a particular geographic location, etc.). However, such information does not identify you individually.

(d) Affiliates; Change of Control. We may share Non-Personal Information and Personal Information with entities controlling, controlled by, or under common control with Bluelink Marekting. In the event that Bluelink Marekting is merged, sold, or in the event of a transfer of some or all of our assets, we may disclose or transfer Non-Personal Information and Personal Information in connection with such transaction.

(e) Other. In certain instances we may disclose Non-Personal Information or Personal Information when we believe it is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against persons or entities in order to protect Bluelink Marekting or our users or when we believe that the law or legal process requires such disclosure.

#### 4\. Third Party Links.

The Bluelink Marekting Website may contain links to websites or content operated and maintained by third parties, over which we have no control. You access such third-party websites or content at your own risk. You should always read the privacy policy of a third-party website before disclosing any information to the website.

#### 5\. Public Forums.

Please be advised that, whenever you voluntarily post information to any Bluelink Marekting community page or any other public forums, such information can and may be accessed by the public. This means that any person or entity with access to such information can potentially use it for any purpose, including sending unsolicited communications.

#### 6\. Security.

Information that we collect is stored on servers that Bluelink Marekting solely manages, using standard security procedures and practices appropriate to the nature of the information in an effort to protect information from unauthorized access, destruction, use, modification, or disclosure. However, No data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect information transmitted on or through the Bluelink Marekting Website, we cannot and do not guarantee or warrant the security of any information you transmit on or through the Bluelink Marekting Website, and you do so at your own risk.

#### 7\. Children's Privacy Statement

We do not knowingly collect Personal Information from children under the age of 13. If we become aware that we have inadvertently received Personal Information from a child under the age of 13, we will delete such information from our records.

#### 8\. Processing in the United States.

Please be aware that Personal Information may be transferred to and maintained on, servers or databases located outside your state, province, country, or other jurisdiction where the privacy laws may not be as protective as those in your location. If you are located outside of the United States, please be advised that we process and store all information in the United States and your consent to this Privacy Policy represents your agreement and understanding to this processing.

#### 9\. Privacy Policy Changes.

From time to time, we may change this Privacy Policy. If we decide to change this Privacy Policy, in whole or in part, we will inform you by posting the revised Privacy Policy on the Bluelink Marekting Website. Those changes will go into effect on the Effective Date disclosed at the end of the revised Privacy Policy. Your continued use of the Bluelink Marekting Website constitutes your agreement to abide by the Privacy Policy as revised. If you object to any such revisions, your sole recourse shall be to stop using the Bluelink Marekting Website.

Effective Date: January 1 2014
